http://www.clutch-specialists.co.uk/pages/privacy

Privacy
Clutch Specialists knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting Clutch Specialists, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.
What personal information about customers does Clutch Specialists gather?
The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at Clutch Specialists. Here are the types of information we gather.
Information you give us
We receive and store any information you enter on our website or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you.
Automatic information
We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses Clutch Specialists. Scroll to the bottom of this page to see examples of the information we receive. A number of companies offer utilities designed to help you visit Web sites anonymously. Although we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience at Clutch Specialists if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these tools exist.
E-mail communications
To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Clutch Specialists if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your account to reflect this by selecting unsubscribed in the newsletters menu.
Information from other sources
For reasons such as improving personalization of our service (for example, providing better product recommendations or special offers that we think will interest you), we might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. We also sometimes receive updated delivery and address information from our shippers or other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily.
What about cookies?
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as automatic login and permanent shopping carts for storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits.
The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of Clutch Specialists's coolest features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on.
Does Clutch Specialists share the information it receives?
Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only with the subsidiaries Clutch Specialists controls and as described below.
Affiliated businesses we do not control
We work closely with our affiliated businesses. In some cases, these businesses operate stores at Clutch Specialists or sell offerings to you at Clutch Specialists. In other cases, we operate stores, provide services, or sell product lines jointly with these businesses. You can tell when another business is involved in your transactions, and we share customer information related to those transactions with that business.
Agents
We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
Promotional offers
Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of Clutch Specialists customers on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not give that business your name and address. If you do not want to receive such offers, please adjust your account newsletter preference as that is how we will send out our promotions.
Business transfers
As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores or assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event that Clutch Specialists, or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.
Protection of Clutch Specialists and others
We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Clutch Specialists, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
With your consent
Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.
How secure is information about me?
Clutch Specialists protects your privacy and information by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. Credit Card Numbers are removed from our server immediatly after the transaction has been made.
It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.
What information can I access?
Clutch Specialists gives you access to the following information about you for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information. This list will change as our Web site evolves.
View your details
What choices do I have?
As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of such Clutch Specialists features as Automatic login, and permanent shopping carts. You can add or update certain information on pages such as those listed in the "My Account" pages. When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records.
If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your account to reflect this in the newsletter menu.
Conditions of use, notices, and revisions
If you choose to visit Clutch Specialists, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the United Kingdom. If you have any concern about privacy at Clutch Specialists, please send us a thorough description to info@clutch-specialists.co.uk, and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly. This Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes.
Information you give us
You provide most such information when you search, buy, bid, post, participate in a contest or questionnaire, or communicate with customer service. For example, you provide information when you search for a product; make an order; provide information in Your Account (and you might have more than one if you have used more than one e-mail address when shopping with us); communicate with us by phone, e-mail, or otherwise; complete a questionnaire or a contest entry form; by providing employer, school, or other such information; participate in Discussion Boards; provide and rate Reviews. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, and phone number; people to whom purchases have been shipped, including address and phone number; other people; content of reviews and e-mails to us; and financial information, including Social Security and driver's license numbers.
Automatic information
Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; purchase history; the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; cookie number; and products you viewed or searched for.
Product successfully added to your Shopping Cart
Continue Shopping
Proceed to Checkout
Sample Product
Quantity
Add to cart
Twitter
Facebook
